





Phone: +52 5579405115 bryanfragoso94@gmail.com LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/bryanfragoso

Ciudad de México

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF LAW

University UNAM 2013-2018

MASTER IN DATA SCIENCE

DEVF SCHOOL 2023-2024

SOFT SKILLS

- Critical Thinking
- Problem-Solving
- Attention to Detail
- Communication
- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Adaptability
- Curiosity

PROFILE

Passionate Data Science professional with experience in various Machine Learning projects. I possess skills in programming languages such as Python, as well knowledge of relational database SQL. My education includes a foundation in mathematics and statistics, complementing my technical skills and problem-solving focus. Additionally, I have experience with visualization tools like Power BI.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Advisor on Property Regularization Matters.

Despacho González y Asociados | Cdmx | 2022 - 2023

- At Despacho González y Asociados, the firm was seeking to enhance its growth strategy through better data-driven decision-making.
- I was tasked with implementing a methodology to improve the firm's growth based on the analysis of Key Performance Indicators (KPIs).
- I introduced the OKR (Objectives and Key Results) methodology. This involved identifying critical KPIs, designing data analysis processes.
- The adoption of the OKR methodology led to a 20% increase in client acquisition within the first six months and improved internal alignment on growth targets, resulting in a more strategic and data-driven approach to business development.

Visualization Project - Public Property Registry, Mexico City May 2019 — July 2022

In this project, I was in charge of the database of the files at the Public Property Registry of Mexico City.

- As an analyst at the Public Property Registry, I was tasked with improving the management and accessibility of property records.
- I was responsible for designing and managing a comprehensive database for the registry files
- I utilized excel to create the database structure, implemented ETL processes using Python to extract, transform, and load data from various sources, and developed interactive data visualizations with Power BI.
- These efforts resulted in a 30% reduction in the time required to access document information and a 20% increase in record accuracy

EXPERIENCE

Machine Learning Projects for Return on Investment Identification

LANGUAGES

- Spanish(Native)
- English(fluent)

INTERESTS

Dance and Music

Japanese Culture

Calisthenics Exercise

New Technologies

Video Games

SKILLS

- Programming Language: Python
- Relational Databases: SQL
- Experience in Visualization Tools: Tableau
- Experience in Exploratory Data Analysis (EDA) of Databases
- Implementation of Machine Learning Models
- Data-Driven Decision-Making Optimization
- Knowledge at Mathematics and Statistics

EXTRAS

FREE CONSULTATION FOR VULNERABLE GROUPS RPPYC CDMX | 2019-2022

• Conducted legal advisory sessions for property regularization to people with disabilities, the elderly, pregnant women, and those with children.

ACTIVE MEMBER OF THE BOOTCAMP XPERIENCE

Bootcamp remote | 2023 - active

Part of a community of data analysts from across Latin America, where we develop EDA and Machine Learning projects implemented for different industry sectors.